NINA REMONDINO

4911 ½ NIAGARA AVE • SAN DIEGO, CA 92107 (516) 314-4121 • NREMONDINO@GMAIL.COM • WWW.NINAJEAN.ME

SUMMARY

High-energy, confident professional with an infectious enthusiasm. Possess a natural ability to sell and build rapport through listening and communication skills. Self-motivated and organized with over 6 years of experience and success in a number of highly successful businesses.

EXPERIENCE

ALLEGRIA HOTEL • LONG BEACH, NY

GUEST SERVICE AGENT/CONCIERGE/RESERVATIONS/PBX

7/2014-1/2015

- Increased sales revenue by upselling rooms and packages
- Assisted guests in completing registration and assigned room accommodation requests
- Built and maintained strong relationships with all customers, as well as worked closely with upper management team members to align company goals to benefit the hotel
- Coordinated with the events team to ensure a smooth process between catering and guest management
- Performed cashiering tasks such as bill and invoice settlement, posted charges to guest folio, and handled payouts
- Accommodated groups to ensure optimal levels of guest satisfaction and repeat business
- Adapted usual protocol for extra VIP guests and synchronized scheduling to accommodate their extended needs
- Liaison with housekeeping for checkouts, stay-overs, and vacancies to keep room status reports up to date
- Responded and took necessary action on guest complaints, issues, and concerns
- Logged all guests' requests into the log book and PMS system as well as followed up to ensure their needs were satisfied
- Managed all incoming calls, and directed them to the proper department
- Ensured all wake-up calls are completed on time
- Answered reservation calls and accommodated guest requests, such as handicap needs, early check-in, connecting rooms etc.
- Transferred 3rd party website reservations to OPERA
- Pre-blocked all VIP guests and airlines, and created welcome packets

BROOKESTONE • NEW YORK, NY

KEY HOLDER/SALES ASSOCIATE

11/2011-12/2012

- Knowledgeable about all products sold in store which helped aid in generating sales in achieving optimal customer satisfaction
- Set and reached daily sales goals including high priced items worth thousands of dollars
- Oversaw and managed sales floor including employees layout and breaks
- Created weekly schedule for all staff
- Trained for managerial promotion
- Directed and trained new employees
- Strengthened customer service and sales skills
- Closed ending register up to \$10,000

EDUCATION

PACE UNIVERSITY 9/2010-12/2014

BA in Business Management with a focus in Entrepreneurship

WELLINGTON C. MEPHAM HIGH SCHOOL

9/2006-6/2010

Advanced Regents Diploma